What is forgotten will never be found.
The Wretched is a horror, mystery, thriller film directed by Drew T. Pierce.
A rebellious teenage boy, struggling with his parents' imminent divorce, encounters a terrifying evil
after his next-door neighbor becomes possessed by an ancient witch that feasts on children.
Ben, played by John-Paul Howard.
Mallory, played by Piper Curda.
Liam, played by Jamison Jones.
Sara, played by Azie Tesfai.
Ty, played by Kevin Bigley.
JJ, played by Gabriella Quezada.
The Wretched is a 2019 American supernatural horror film
written and directed by the Pierce Brothers.
It stars John-Paul Howard, Piper Curda, Zarah Mahler, Kevin Bigley, Gabriela Quezada
Bloomgarden, Richard Ellis, Blane Crockarell, Jamison Jones, and Azie Tesfai.
The film follows a defiant teenage boy who faces off with an
evil witch posing as the neighbor next door.
The Wretched had its world premiere at the Fantasia International Film Festival on July 19,
2019, and was released in drive-in theaters and through Premium VOD on May 1, 2020.
Due to the COVID-19 pandemic limiting the number of films in theaters, it became the first
film since Avatar (2009) to top the box office for six consecutive weekends.
The film explores themes of witch, possession, woods, neighbor, marine.
The tone is intense and dark and mind_bending.